PORTFOLIO

- UI/UX Graphic Design: http://mrmatthes.com/index.php/design/
- Illustrations: http://mrmatthes.com/index.php/illustration/

ABOUT

I have 7+ years of overall design experience. I am a senior UI/UX Designer and Graphic Artist with a focus on user friendly and creative designs with 5+ years of experience on both web and mobile platforms. I have experience with modern UI/UX tools (Adobe Creative Suite, WPF, After Effects, Adobe XD, Figma, and Sketch) and, as I have done in the past, work well with software engineering teams. Additionally, I have vast experience creating Graphic Art through digital painting or by hand, collaborating with art directors and clients.

EXPERIENCE

Advantaa Computer, Irvine, CA - Senior UI/UX Designer

MAY 2015 - PRESENT

- Built UI designs on enterprise grade hosted VDI with fully adobe suite from Photoshop to XD.
- Held close contact with the software team and had a leadership role in the management and development of the UI and UX.
- Interfaced with customers to gather feedback on the designs. Modified the UI/UX according to the feedback.
- Built animations for marketing materials with Adobe Premiere.
- Designed and helped develop the main company website.
- Worked on the same scrum and agile cycle as developers did.

Massage Matters - Lead Graphic Designer

Sep 2020 - PRESENT

- Built custom signs, business cards, and other printed materials.
- Maintained brand identity.
- Work alongside management. Editing and creating designs according to feedback.
- Helped design the main website and several icons.

Consulting, Dana Point - Graphic Design Consultant

May 2015 - PRESENT

- Novvum Created UI/UX interface for landing pages.
- Corteze Socks Created amazon ads and assisted with sock designs.
- Ocean Inspired Help with web presence as well as business branding.
- Screen Print Assistant (David Blake) Worked alongside Artist performing full screen print process.
- Senor Barber Business cards
- Children's Cerebral Palsy Movement (CCPM) Created flyers for events.

EDUCATION

Laguna College of Art And Design, Laguna Beach — Bachelor's Degree in Graphic Design

3D, packaging design, UI UX, advertising, photography, and video

Laguna College of Art And Design, Laguna Beach — Bachelor's Degree in Illustration

Print, advertising, web, motion, video, package, action sport design